("All Night Long"
by Lionel Richie)
♪ Da da
♪ Oh oh
♪ Well, my friends,
the time has come ♪
♪ Raise the roof
and have some fun ♪
♪ Throw away the
work to be done ♪
♪ Let the music play on
♪ Everybody sing,
everybody dance ♪
♪ Lose yourself
in wild romance ♪
♪ We going to party,
karamu, fiesta, forever ♪
♪ Come on and sing along
♪ We're going to party,
karamu, fiesta, forever ♪
♪ Come on and sing along
♪ All night long, (all night)
all night (all night) ♪
♪ All night long
(all night, all night) ♪
♪ Yeah, once you get
started you can't sit down ♪
♪ Come join the fun,
it's a merry-go-round ♪
♪ Everyone's dancing
their troubles away ♪
♪ Come join our party,
see how we play ♪
♪ Tom bo li de say de moi
ya, yeah, jambo jambo ♪
♪ Way to parti o we
goin', oh, jambali ♪
♪ Tom bo li de say de moi
ya, yeah, jambo jambo ♪
♪ Oh, yes
♪ We're gonna have
a party, yeah, uh ♪
♪ All night long, (all night)
all night (all night) ♪
yes (all night) ♪
♪ All night long, (all night)
all night (all night) ♪
♪ All night long (all night)
♪ Whoa, uh (all night)
♪ Everyone you meet, they're
jamming in the street ♪
♪ All night long (all night)
♪ Yeah, I said (all night)
♪ Everyone you meet (all night)
♪ They're jamming in
the street (all night) ♪
♪ All night long
(all night, all night) ♪
♪ Feel good, feel good
♪ (All night, all night)
♪ (All night)